Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: New American Library, Editorial/Author Files
  - Fadiman, Edwin, "The 21" Screen,", 1956-1960 (Box 36, Folder 566)
  - Fadiman, Edwin, and Adela Rogers St. Johns, "The Jean Harlow Story,", 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 567)
  - Fairservis, Walter, general correspondence, "Pre-History of India,", 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 568)
  - Fairservis, Walter, "Origins of Oriental Civilization,", 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 569)
  - Fairservis, Walter, "The Wonders of Ancient Nubia,", 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 570)
  - Fall, Thomas, "The Prettiest Girl in Town,", 1953-1956 (Box 36, Folder 571)
  - Fannie Farmer's Handy Cookbook, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 572)
  - Fannie Farmer's Handy Cookbook, 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 573)
  - Farrar, Larston, general file, 1957-1960 (Box 37, Folder 574)
  - Farrar, Larston, "The Sins of Sandra Shaw,", 1957 (Box 37, Folder 575)
  - Farrar, Larston, "Washington Lowdown,", 1955 (Box 37, Folder 576)
  - Farrar, Larston, "Washington Lowdown,", 1956 (Box 37, Folder 577)
  - Farrar, Larston, "Washington Lowdown,", 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 578)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 579)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 580)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 37, Folder 581)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 37, Folder 582)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 583)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 584)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 585)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 586)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 587)
  - (no file), undated (Box 37, Folder 588)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 589)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 590)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 591)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 592)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 593)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 594)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 595)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 596)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 597)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 598)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 599)
  - Farrell, James T., general correspondence, undated (Box 37, Folder 600)
  - Farrell, James T., general contracts, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 601)
  - Farrell, James T., general statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 602)
  - Farrell, James T., "An American Dream Girl,", 1950-1953 (Box 37, Folder 603)
  - Farrell, James T., "Bernard Carr,", 1950-1955 (Box 37, Folder 604)
  - Farrell, James T., "A Dangerous Woman,", 1955-1959 (Box 37, Folder 605)
  - Farrell, James T., "Ellen Rogers,", 1949-1958 (Box 37, Folder 606)
  - Farrell, James T., "The Face of Time,", 1955 (Box 37, Folder 607)
  - Farrell, James T., "Father and Son,", 1953 (Box 37, Folder 608)
  - Farrell, James T., "French Girls are Vicious,", 1946-1958 (Box 37, Folder 609)
  - Farrell, James T., "Judgment Day,", 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 610)
  - Farrell, James T., "The Life Adventurous,", 1950-1954 (Box 37, Folder 611)
  - Farrell, James T., "Meet the Girls,", 1947-1949 (Box 37, Folder 612)
  - Farrell, James T., "My Days of Anger,", 1954 (Box 37, Folder 613)
  - Farrell, James T., "No Star is Lost,", 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 614)
  - Farrell, James T., "An Old Sweetheart,", 1958 (Box 37, Folder 615)
  - Farrell, James T., "The Road Between,", 1954 (Box 37, Folder 616)
  - Farrell, James T., "Saturday Night,", 1950-1959 (Box 37, Folder 617)
  - Farrell, James T., "Studs Lonigan,", 1957-1961 (Box 37, Folder 618)
  - Farrell, James T., "$10,000 a Week and Other Stories,", 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 619)
  - Farrell, James T., "This Man and This Woman,", 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 620)
  - Farrell, James T., "A Universe of Time,", 1958 (Box 37, Folder 621)
  - Farrell, James T., "When Boyhood Dreams Come True,", 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 622)
  - Farrell, James T., "A World I Never Made,", 1952 (Box 37, Folder 623)
  - Farrell, James T., "Yet Other Waters,", 1954 (Box 37, Folder 624)
  - Farrell, James T., "Young Lonigan,", 1947-1955 (Box 37, Folder 625)
  - Farrell, James T., "Young Manhood of Studs Lonigan,", 1949-1958 (Box 37, Folder 626)
  - Fast, Julius, "Out of this World,", 1944-1956 (Box 38, Folder 627)
  - Faulkner, William, general correspondence, 1946-1960 (Box 38, Folder 628)
  - Faulkner, William, "Intruder in the Dust,", 1949-1960 (Box 38, Folder 629)
  - Faulkner, William, "Knight's Gambit,", 1950-1956 (Box 38, Folder 630)
  - Faulkner, William, "The Long Hot Summer" ["The Hamlet"], 1957-1959 (Box 38, Folder 631)
  - Faulkner, William, "Pylon,", 1946-1960 (Box 38, Folder 632)
  - Faulkner, William, "Sanctuary,", 1946-1953 (Box 38, Folder 633)
  - Faulkner, William, "Sanctuary," "Requiem for a Nun,", 1953-1960 (Box 38, Folder 634)
  - Faulkner, William, "Sartoris,", 1951-1961 (Box 38, Folder 635)
  - Faulkner, William, "Soldier's Pay,", 1951-1959 (Box 38, Folder 636)
  - Faulkner, William, "The Sound and the Fury,", 1951-1958 (Box 38, Folder 637)
  - Faulkner, William, "The Unvanquished,", 1951-1961 (Box 38, Folder 638)
  - Faulkner, William, "The Wild Palms,", 1947-1950 (Box 38, Folder 639)
  - Faulkner, William, "The Wild Palms," "The Old Man,", 1953-1959 (Box 38, Folder 640)
  - Feibleman, Peter, "A Place Without Twilight," "Daughters of Necessity,", 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 641)
  - Fenner, Phyllis, "Something Shared,", 1958 (Box 38, Folder 642)
  - Ferguson, John, "Stealthy Terror,", 1947 (Box 38, Folder 643)
  - Fernandez-Flora, Dario, "Lola,", 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 644)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion, "Jephta and his Daughter,", 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 645)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion, "Raquel,", 1955-1958 (Box 38, Folder 646)
  - Fielding, Henry, "Joseph Andrews," "Jonathan Wild,", 1961 (Box 38, Folder 647)
  - Fine, Benjamin, "1,000,000 Delinquents,", 1955-1959 (Box 38, Folder 648)
  - Finnegan, Robert, 'The Bandaged Nude,", 1950-1956 (Box 38, Folder 649)
  - Firth, Raymond, "Human Types,", 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 650)
  - Fischer, Bruno, general correspondence, "The Bleeding Scissors,", 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 651)
  - Fischer, Bruno, "The Flesh Was Cold," "The Restless Hands,", 1949-1957 (Box 38, Folder 652)
  - Fischer, Bruno, "The Silent Dust," "Stripped for Murder,", 1950-1953 (Box 38, Folder 653)
  - Fischer, Louis, "Gandhi,", 1953 (Box 38, Folder 654)
  - Fischer, Louis, "Gandhi,", 1954 (Box 38, Folder 655)
  - Fischer, Louis, "Gandhi,", 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 655.A)
  - Fisher, Robert Moore, "How to Know and Predict the Weather,", 1951-1959 (Box 38, Folder 656)
  - Fisher, William, "The Waiters,", 1951-1957 (Box 38, Folder 657)
  - Fjelde, Rolf, "Ibsen,", 1959 (Box 38, Folder 658)
  - Flaiano, Ennio, "The Short Cut,", 1950-1960 (Box 38, Folder 659)
  - Flaubert, Gustave, "Madame Bovary,", 1960 (Box 38, Folder 660)
  - Fleming, Ian, general correspondence, "Casino Royale," "Diamonds Are Forever," "Dr. No,", 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 661)
  - Fleming, Ian, "For Your Eyes Only," "From Russia, With Love,", 1957-1961 (Box 38, Folder 662)
  - Fleming, Ian, "Goldfinger," "Live and Let Die," "Moonraker," "Thunderball,", 1959-1960 (Box 38, Folder 663)
  - Flood, Charles Bracelan, "Love is a Bridge,", 1953-1960 (Box 38, Folder 664)
  - Flora, Fletcher, "Donna," "Whispers of the Flesh," ["Wake With a Stranger," "Restless Lovers"], 1957-1959 (Box 38, Folder 665)
  - Foote, Shelby, general correspondence, "Anthology of Civil War Stories,", 1952-1957 (Box 38, Folder 666)
  - Foote, Shelby, "Follow Me Down,", 1950-1959 (Box 38, Folder 667)
  - Foote, Shelby, "Love in a Dry Season," "Shilo,", 1951-1954 (Box 38, Folder 668)
  - Footner, Hulbert, "Death of a Saboteur,", 1957 (Box 38, Folder 669)
  - Foreman, L.L., general correspondence, "Gunsmoke Men," "Lobo Grey,", 1957-1961 (Box 38, Folder 670)
  - Forster, E.M., "A Passage to India,", 1946-1955 (Box 38, Folder 671)
  - Foster, Joseph, general correspondence, "A Cow is Too Much Trouble...," "Street of the Barefoot Lovers...,", 1953-1957 (Box 38, Folder 672)
  - Fradon, Dana, "The Cartoon Book,", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 673)
  - Frame, Donald, "Voltaire," "Manon Lescaut,", 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 674)
  - Francis, William, general correspondence, "Kill or Cure,", 1950-1952 (Box 39, Folder 675)
  - Frank, Lawrence K., general correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 39, Folder 676)
  - Frank, Lawrence K. and Mary, "How to Help Your Child in School,", 1950-1954 (Box 39, Folder 677)
  - Frank, Lawrence K. and Mary, "Your Adolescent at Home and School,", 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 678)
  - Frank, Leonhard, general correspondence, "Desire Me,", 1947-1952 (Box 39, Folder 679)
  - Frank, Leonhard, "Desire Me" (film pictorial) (no date), undated (Box 39, Folder 680)
  - Frankel, Ernest, "Band of Brothers,", 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 681)
  - Franzero, Carlo Mario, "Cleopatra,", 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 682)
  - Frazier, Sir James, "The New Golden Bough,", 1959 (Box 39, Folder 683)
  - Frede, Richard, "Entry E,", 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 684)
  - Frederics, Diana, "Diana,", 1949-1955 (Box 39, Folder 685)
  - Freeman, Lucy, "Troubled Women,", 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 686)
  - Freeman, Walter, "All the Way Home,", 1953-1958 (Box 39, Folder 687)
  - Freeman, Walter, "The Golden Oasis,", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 688)
  - Freeman, Walter, "The Last Blitzkreig,", 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 689)
  - Fremantle, Anne, general correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 690)
  - Fremantle, Anne, general correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 39, Folder 691)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Age of Belief,", 1955-1961 (Box 39, Folder 692)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Age of Belief" ["The Age of Faith"], 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 693)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Age of Belief,", 1954 (Box 39, Folder 694)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Age of Belief,", 1954 (Box 39, Folder 695)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Age of Belief,", 1954 (Box 39, Folder 696)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Papal Encyclicals,", 1956-1961 (Box 39, Folder 697)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Papal Encyclicals,", 1956 (Box 39, Folder 698)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Papal Encyclicals,", 1956 (Box 39, Folder 699)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Papal Encyclicals,", 1954-1955 (Box 39, Folder 700)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "The Indwelling Spirit," "Mao Tse-Tung,", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 701)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "This Little Band of Prophets,", 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 702)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "This Little Band of Prophets,", 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 703)
  - Fremantle, Anne, "A Treasury of Early Christianity,", 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 704)
  - Freud, Sigmund, general correspondence [Montagu, Ashley], 1947-1951 (Box 39, Folder 704.A)
  - Freud, Sigmund, "The Interpretation of Dreams,", 1950 (Box 39, Folder 705)
  - Freud, Sigmund, "Psychopathology of Everyday Life,", 1951-1960 (Box 39, Folder 706)
  - Fruje, August, "Art and Artists,", 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 707)
  - Fuller, Robert, "Danger - Marines at Work,", 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 708)
  - Furcolowe, Charles, general correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 39, Folder 709)
  - Furcolowe, Charles, "Search for the Sun,", 1952-1957 (Box 39, Folder 710)
  - Gaby, Alex, "To End the Night,", 1951-1957 (Box 39, Folder 711)
  - Gaddis, Thomas E., "Birdman of Alcatraz,", 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 712)
  - Gaddis, Thomas E., "Birdman of Alcatraz,", 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 713)
  - Gaddis, Thomas E., "Birdman of Alcatraz,", 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 714)
  - Gaer, Joseph, general correspondence, 1955-1961 (Box 40, Folder 715)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "American Roots in the Bible,", 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 716)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "How the Great Religions Began,", 1955-1961 (Box 40, Folder 717)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "How the Great Religions Began,", 1953-1954 (Box 40, Folder 718)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "The Wandering Jew,", 1959-1962 (Box 40, Folder 719)
  - Gaer, Joseph, "The Wandering Jew,", 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 720)
  - Gaines, William, "The Bedside Mad,", 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 721)
  - Gaines, William, "Mad [various],", 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 722)
  - Gaines, William, "Like Mad," "Mad's Maddest Artist," "Organization Mad,", 1960 (Box 40, Folder 723)
  - Gaines, William, "Son of Mad,", 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 724)
  - Gallico, Paul, "The Lonely,", 1950-1959 (Box 40, Folder 725)
  - Gamow, George, "The Birth and Death of the Sun,", 1946-1960 (Box 41, Folder 726)
  - Gamow, George, "Biography of the Earth,", 1947-1960 (Box 41, Folder 727)
  - Gamow, George, "The Creation of the Universe,", 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 728)
  - Gamow, George, "Infinity,", 1953-1961 (Box 41, Folder 729)
  - Gant, Matthew [Arnold Hano], general correspondence, "The International Traveling Salesman,", 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 730)
  - Gant, Matthew, "The Manhunter,", 1956-1961 (Box 41, Folder 731)
  - Gant, Matthew, "The Raven and the Sword,", 1958-1961 (Box 41, Folder 732)
  - Garland, George [Garland Roark], general correspondence, "Apache Warpath," "The Big Dry," "Doubtful Valley,", 1957-1959 (Box 41, Folder 733)
  - Garner, Claude, "Cornbread Aristocrat," "Woamn in Oil,", 1950-1961 (Box 41, Folder 734)
  - Garrett, George, "The Finished Man," "King of the Mountain,", 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 735)
  - Garrity, Devon A.., "The Irish Genius," "Mentor Book of Irish Poetry,", 1959-1961 (Box 41, Folder 736)
  - Gault, William Campbell, "The Hundred Dollar Girl,", 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 737)
  - Gazzo, Michael Vincent, "A Hatful of Rain,", 1957 (Box 41, Folder 738)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1948-1960 (Box 41, Folder 739)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1954 (Box 41, Folder 740)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1953 (Box 41, Folder 741)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1953 (Box 41, Folder 742)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1951-1952 (Box 41, Folder 743)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report,", 1948 (Box 41, Folder 744)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report" (drafts, etc.) (no date), undated (Box 41, Folder 745)
  - Geddes, Donald, "About the Kinsey Report" (clips, reviews), undated (Box 41, Folder 746)
  - Gehman, Richard, general correspondence, "A Murder in Paradise," "The Slander of Witches,", 1953-1958 (Box 41, Folder 747)
  - Gerson, Noel, Lola Montez project, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 747.A)
  - Ghiselin, Brewster, "The Creative Process,", 1953-1960 (Box 41, Folder 748)
  - Gibb, H.A.R., "Mohammedanism,", 1953-1959 (Box 41, Folder 749)
  - Gibson, Jewel, "Black Gold,", 1950-1956 (Box 41, Folder 750)
  - Gilbert, G.M., "Nuremberg Diary,", 1961 (Box 41, Folder 751)
  - Gillon, Philip, "Frail Barrier,", 1951-1953 (Box 41, Folder 752)
  - Gilman, Peter, general correspondence, "Big Sur,", 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 753)
  - Gilman, Peter, "Diamond Head,", 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 754)
  - Gilman, Peter, "Diamond Head,", 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 755)
  - Ginger, Ray, "Six Days or Forever,", 1958-1961 (Box 41, Folder 756)
  - Gissing, G.R., "The Private Papers of Henry Ryecroft,", 1961 (Box 41, Folder 757)
  - Glemser, Bernard, "Gallery of Women,", 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 758)
  - Gluckman, Max, "Social Anthropology,", 1959-1961 (Box 41, Folder 759)
  - Glyn, Anthony, "I Can Take It All,", 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 760)
  - Goethe, "The Sorrows of Young Werther,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 761)
  - Gogol, Nikolai, "Dead Souls," "Diary of a Madman,", 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 762)
  - Gold, Herbert, "The Prospect Before Us" ["Room Clerk"], 1953-1960 (Box 42, Folder 763)
  - Gold, Ivan (untitled), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 764)
  - Goldat, George, and Seyyed H. Nasr, "History of Science Series,", 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 765)
  - Golden, Milton, "Hollywood Lawyer,", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 766)
  - Goldhurst, Richard, "The Deceivers" ["The Bear Went Over the Mountain"], 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 767)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1957-1959 (Box 42, Folder 768)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1954-1960 (Box 42, Folder 769)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 770)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1957 (Box 42, Folder 771)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1954-1957 (Box 42, Folder 772)
  - Goldin, Judah, "The Living Talmud,", 1955-1957 (Box 42, Folder 773)
  - Goldsmith, Martin, "The Sixth Confessor,", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 774)
  - Goldsmith, Oscar, "The Vicar of Wakefield,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 774.A)
  - Goldwin, Robert, and Charles Nelson, "Toward the Liberally Educated Executive,", 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 775)
  - Goldwin, Robert, and Charles Nelson, "Toward the Liberally Educated Executive,", 1959 (Box 42, Folder 776)
  - Goncharov, Ivan [trans. Ann Dunnigan], "Oblomov,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 777)
  - Goodman, Mitchell, "Man is a Hunter,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 778)
  - Goodrich, Norma, "The Ancient Myths,", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 779)
  - Goodrich, Norma, "The Medieval Myths,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 780)
  - Goodwin, Peggy, "The Lie,", 1953-1955 (Box 42, Folder 781)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, "The Lying Days," "The Soft Voice of the Serpent,", 1951-1959 (Box 42, Folder 782)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, manuscripts, undated (Box 42, Folder 783)
  - Gorham, Charles, "The Future Mr. Dolan," "The Gilded Hearse,", 1949-1955 (Box 42, Folder 784)
  - Gorham, Charles, "The Gold of Their Bodies," "Trial by Darkness,", 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 785)
  - Goulet, Robert, "Charivari,", 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 786)
  - Grady, Erwin, "The Fine Line,", 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 787)
  - Graham, Jay and Edwin Olmstead, "The Unsinkable Mr. Jay,", 1959 (Box 42, Folder 788)
  - Grahame, Kenneth, "The Wind in the Willows,", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 789)
  - Granberry, Edwin, "Strangers and Lovers,", 1950-1959 (Box 42, Folder 790)
  - Grant, Michael, "The World of Rome,", 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 791)
  - Grau, Shirley Ann, "The Black Prince,", 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 792)
  - Grau, Shirley Ann, general correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 793)
  - Green, Julian, "Moira,", 1950-1952 (Box 42, Folder 794)
  - Greene, Joe, "To the Dedicated Few,", 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 795)
  - Greene, John C., "The Death of Adam,", 1959-1961 (Box 42, Folder 796)
  - Gregory, Horace, "The Mentor Book of Religious Verse,", 1956-1959 (Box 42, Folder 797)
  - Gregory, Horace, "Metamorphoses of Ovid,", 1959-1961 (Box 42, Folder 798)
  - Gresham, William Lindsay, "Limbo Tower," "Nightmare Alley,", 1948-1960 (Box 42, Folder 799)
  - Grey, Harry, "The Hoods,", 1951-1959 (Box 42, Folder 800)
  - Grey, Harry, "Portrait of a Mobster", undated (Box 42, Folder 801)
  - Griffin, John Howard, "The Devil Rides Outside,", 1952-1959 (Box 42, Folder 802)
  - Groddeck, Georg, "The Book of It,", 1961 (Box 42, Folder 803)
  - Grosser, Maurice, "The Painter's Eye,", 1951-1959 (Box 42, Folder 804)
  - Gruber, Frank, general correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 43, Folder 805)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Fourth Letter," "French Key Mysteries," 1949-50, 1958, 1949-1958 (Box 43, Folder 806)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Gamecock Murders," "Gift Horse," 1948-58, 1958, 1948-1958 (Box 43, Folder 807)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Homest Dealers," "Hungry Dog Murders,", 1947, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 808)
  - Gruber, Frank, "A Job of Murder" ["The Leather Duke"], 1949-1950 (Box 43, Folder 809)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Laughing Fox,", 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 810)
  - Gruber, Frank, "Market for Murder,", 1947 (Box 43, Folder 811)
  - Gruber, Frank, "Mighty Blockhead," "Navy Colt,", 1958 (Box 43, Folder 812)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Silver Jackass,", 1946-1951 (Box 43, Folder 813)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Silver Tombstone,", 1946-1958 (Box 43, Folder 814)
  - Gruber, Frank, "Simon Lash, Private Detective,", 1951 (Box 43, Folder 815)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Talking Clock,", 1946-1948 (Box 43, Folder 816)
  - Gruber, Frank, "The Whispering Master,", 1948-1958 (Box 43, Folder 817)
  - Gulick, Bill, "The Land Beyond,", 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 818)
  - Gunn, James, "Deadlier Than the Male,", 1948-1954 (Box 43, Folder 819)
  - Gunther, Gordon, "Split Level Trap,", 1950 (Box 43, Folder 820)
  - Guss, Jack, "The Scientist Story,", 1959-1961 (Box 43, Folder 821)
  - Gutheim, Frederick, general correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 43, Folder 822)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 823)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F., "Having a Baby," "Pregnancy and Birth,", 1949-1958 (Box 43, Folder 824)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F., "Having a Baby" (ms.), 1946 (Box 43, Folder 825)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F., "Pregnancy and Birth,", 1957-1961 (Box 43, Folder 826)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F., "The Story of Human Birth,", 1945-1949 (Box 43, Folder 827)
  - Habas, Ralph A.., "How to Live Without Liquor,", 1954-1956 (Box 44, Folder 828)
  - Hackett, Marie, "American Beauty," "The Major Herbert Story,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 829)
  - Hackett, Paul, "Five Days in August," "Obscenity," "Rock Bottom,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 830)
  - Hackett, Paul, "Tarpon Springs,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 831)
  - Hackney, Alan, "I'm All Right Jack,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 832)
  - Hadas, Moses [trans.], Plutarch, "On Love, the Family, and the Good Life,", 1956-1959 (Box 44, Folder 833)
  - von Hagen, Victor, general correspondence, 1955-1961 (Box 44, Folder 834)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "The Ancient Sun Kingdoms of the Americas,", 1961 (Box 44, Folder 835)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "The Mochica Empire of Peru,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 836)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "Realm of the Incas,", 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 837)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "Realm of the Maya,", 1957-1961 (Box 44, Folder 838)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "The World of the Maya,", 1958-1960 (Box 44, Folder 839)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "The World of the Maya,", 1958-1960 (Box 44, Folder 840)
  - von Hagen, Victor, "The World of the Maya,", 1958-1960 (Box 44, Folder 841)
  - Hahn, Emily [Banda McCloud], "Indo," "Mata Hari's Daughter,", 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 842)
  - Haile, Pennington, "The Eagle and the Bear,", 1950-1951 (Box 44, Folder 843)
  - Hales, Norman [Vernon Young], "The Spider and the Cup,", 1954-1958 (Box 44, Folder 844)
  - Hall, Calvin S., "A Primer of Freudian Psychology,", 1954-1961 (Box 44, Folder 845)
  - Hall, David, "Good Listening,", 1950-1951 (Box 44, Folder 846)
  - Hall, James B., "Floodlight," "In the Eye of the Storm,", 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 847)
  - Hall, Rupert, "History of Science,", 1961 (Box 44, Folder 848)
  - Hamilton, Edith, general correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 849)
  - Hamilton, Edith, "The Greek Way,", 1947-1956 (Box 44, Folder 850)
  - Hamilton, Edith, "Mythology,", 1947-1960 (Box 44, Folder 851)
  - Hamilton, Edith, "The Roman Way,", 1957-1961 (Box 44, Folder 852)
  - Hamilton, Edmond, "Beyond the Moon,", 1950-1957 (Box 44, Folder 853)
  - Hamner, Earl (Jr.), "Fifty Roads to Town,", 1953-1956 (Box 44, Folder 854)
  - Hampshire, Stuart, "The Age of Reason,", 1953-1960 (Box 44, Folder 855)
  - Hampshire, Stuart, "The Age of Reason,", 1953-1955 (Box 44, Folder 856)
  - Hampton, Kathleen, "The Patch,", 1960 (Box 44, Folder 857)
  - Han Su Yin, "And the Rain My Drink,", 1956-1960 (Box 44, Folder 858)
  - Han Su Yin, "A Many Splendored Thing,", 1952-1960 (Box 44, Folder 859)
  - Han Su Yin, "The Mountain is Young,", 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 860)
  - Hansberry, Lorraine, "A Raisin in the Sun,", 1958-1961 (Box 44, Folder 861)
  - Hansen, Harry, "History of the Civil War,", 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 862)